{
    "data": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Database System",
                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:09:55.362Z",
                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:10:00.680Z",
                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:10:00.677Z",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 1,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Why we need ER diagrams?",
                                "answer": "Entity-relationship (ER) diagrams are used to model the relationships between entities in a database.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:20:34.709Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:20:36.762Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:20:36.761Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 2,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Different between DB and DBMS?",
                                "answer": "A database (DB) is an organized collection of data, stored and accessed electronically. A database management system (DBMS) is a software application that interacts with the user, other applications, and the database itself to capture and analyze the data.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:23:02.422Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:23:04.044Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:23:04.043Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 3,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the relationship types in relational database?",
                                "answer": "One-to-One, One-to-Many and Many-to-Many",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:27:29.814Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:27:31.630Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:27:31.628Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 4,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is Primary Key in an Entity?",
                                "answer": "In a database, a primary key is a field (or combination of fields) that uniquely identifies each record in a table. The primary key is used to enforce the entity integrity of the table, as it ensures that no two records have the same key value.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:32:04.115Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:32:05.803Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:32:05.800Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 5,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is Foreign Key?",
                                "answer": "A foreign key is a field (or combination of fields) in a database table that refers to the primary key of another table. The purpose of the foreign key is to establish a link between the two tables, allowing data in one table to be related to data in the other table.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:33:34.027Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:33:36.177Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:33:36.176Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 6,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Why we need Normalization?",
                                "answer": "Normalization is the process of organizing a database in a way that reduces redundancy and dependency. It is an important step in database design, as it helps to improve the efficiency, performance, and integrity of the database.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:36:25.178Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:36:27.044Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:36:27.043Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 7,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is DDL?",
                                "answer": "Data Definition Language (DDL) is a subset of SQL that is used to define the database structure or schema. It consists of a set of commands that can be used to create, modify, and delete database objects such as tables, indexes, and sequences.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:39:52.741Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:39:54.724Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:39:54.723Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 8,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is DML?",
                                "answer": "Data Manipulation Language (DML) is a subset of SQL that is used to manage the data stored in a database. It consists of a set of commands that can be used to insert, update, delete, and retrieve data from database tables.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:41:44.178Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:41:46.378Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:41:46.377Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 9,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the popular RDBMS?",
                                "answer": "Oracle, MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL, IBM DB2",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:45:06.162Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:45:08.000Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:45:07.998Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 10,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is NoSQL?",
                                "answer": "NoSQL (short for \"Not Only SQL\") is a term used to describe database management systems that are designed to handle large amounts of data that is not well-suited for a traditional, relational database management system (RDBMS).",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:47:09.948Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:47:11.654Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:47:11.653Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 11,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Examples for NoSQL databases?",
                                "answer": "MongoDB, Cassandra, Redis, Couchbase, Neo4j",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:50:03.446Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:50:05.104Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:50:05.101Z"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Graphic Design",
                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:10:43.810Z",
                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:10:46.275Z",
                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:10:46.273Z",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 12,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Why graphic designing is important?",
                                "answer": "Graphic design is the art and practice of creating visual content to communicate ideas and information. It is an essential aspect of many fields, including advertising, marketing, web design, and user interface design.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T06:56:15.874Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T06:56:17.526Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T06:56:17.525Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 13,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is resolution?",
                                "answer": "In graphic design and digital imaging, resolution refers to the number of pixels or dots per inch (dpi) in an image or display. High resolution images have more pixels or dots per inch, which means that they are more detailed and have a higher level of quality. Low resolution images have fewer pixels or dots per inch, which means that they are less detailed and have a lower level of quality.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T06:58:32.616Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T06:58:34.230Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T06:58:34.229Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 14,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is pixel?",
                                "answer": "A pixel, short for \"picture element,\" is the smallest unit of a digital image. It is a single point of color and brightness that, when viewed from a distance, combines with other pixels to create the overall image. Each pixel has a specific color, represented by a set of numerical values, and a specific location on the image.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:01:36.121Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:01:38.249Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:01:38.247Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 15,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the relation between resolution and pixel?",
                                "answer": "Resolution refers to the total number of pixels in an image, measured in pixels per inch (PPI) for digital images and dots per inch (DPI) for printed images.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:05:13.658Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:05:15.324Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:05:15.323Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 16,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is Raster Graphics?",
                                "answer": "Raster graphics, also known as bitmap graphics, is a type of digital image that is made up of a grid of pixels. Each pixel in a raster image represents a specific color and brightness, and when viewed from a distance, the pixels combine to create the overall image.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:07:56.934Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:07:58.653Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:07:58.651Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 17,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Popular raster graphic softwares?",
                                "answer": "Adobe Photoshop, GIMP",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:10:54.536Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:10:55.851Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:10:55.849Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 18,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is vector graphics?",
                                "answer": "Vector graphics is a type of digital image that is created using mathematical equations to define the shapes, lines, and colors of the image. Unlike raster graphics, which are made up of pixels, vector graphics are resolution independent, which means that they can be enlarged or reduced without losing quality.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:12:25.602Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:12:27.224Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:12:27.222Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 19,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Popular vector graphic softwares?",
                                "answer": "Adobe Illustrator, CorelDRAW, Inkscape, Affinity Designer, Sketch",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:15:13.617Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:15:15.215Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:15:15.212Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 20,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Difference between CMYK and RGB color modes?",
                                "answer": "When you are designing for print, you should use the CMYK color mode, as most printers use CMYK inks. But if you are designing for digital media, you should use RGB color mode as monitors, smartphones and televisions use RGB technology to display colors.",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:20:21.799Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:20:23.687Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:20:23.685Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 21,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the lossy graphic formats?",
                                "answer": "JPEG, GIF, WebP",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:24:33.133Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:24:35.262Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:24:35.260Z"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 22,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the lossless graphic formats?",
                                "answer": "BMP, PNG, RAW",
                                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T07:28:28.597Z",
                                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T07:28:30.256Z",
                                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T07:28:30.255Z"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Software Programming",
                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:11:12.320Z",
                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:11:14.897Z",
                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:11:14.895Z",
                "questions": {
                    "data": []
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Software Testing",
                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:11:42.227Z",
                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:11:43.521Z",
                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:11:43.518Z",
                "questions": {
                    "data": []
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "System Analysis and Design",
                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:12:08.704Z",
                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:12:10.729Z",
                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:12:10.727Z",
                "questions": {
                    "data": []
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Web Programming",
                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:12:39.372Z",
                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:12:41.093Z",
                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:12:41.091Z",
                "questions": {
                    "data": []
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Local Area Network",
                "createdAt": "2023-01-10T05:13:04.129Z",
                "updatedAt": "2023-01-10T05:13:06.177Z",
                "publishedAt": "2023-01-10T05:13:06.176Z",
                "questions": {
                    "data": []
                }
            }
        }
    ],
    "meta": {
        "pagination": {
            "page": 1,
            "pageSize": 25,
            "pageCount": 1,
            "total": 7
        }
    }
}